LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate
the face of light
Save your tears for the day
When our pain is far behind
On your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
Fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
Berlin : a city where corruption and revival coexist.
Here lies one of the few International
cities that was a target for missile attacks
in both the nuclear Third World War
and the conventional Fourth World War.
Even so, this city, which holds special
significance for the Germanic people,
has succeeded in completing a dramatic revival each time,
renewing itself as the nation's capital three times.
Angel's
Poem
Even Kyo-Re's 3003 model thermo-optical
camouflage can't deceive a dog's sense of smell.
What are you doing, Batou?
Stop screwing around if you don't want to mess up.
Sorry, couldn't help myself.
I'm not really suited to these long
surveillance missions in the first place.
Besides, this snow makes things worse.
It reduces the effectiveness of the thermo-optical camouflage.
There aren't that many people who are cut out for these missions.
Let's finish up and get out of here.
They'll reach a conclusion in a few days.
Batou, I'm signing off.
This line may be tapped, even though it's an encrypted transmission.
Get back to your post soon.
Got it.
Even with all my sensory functions
turned off, the cold still gets to me.
I'm surprised you got here in time.
Was there a direct flight from Taiwan?
I first made a stop in Hong Kong and had them
give me a seat on the first flight here.
I'm surprised that we're attempting to
bag such big game with a mixed team.
Yeah.
When I heard about the mission from the Chief,
I actually thought he was joking for a second.
Well. Angel Wing is a major terrorist.
He's been targeting the leaders of developed
nations while they're attending summits.
They might have settled on this capture strategy
as a way to let each nation look good.
And you and I got picked for the dirty work.
The timing of a mission overseas right now...
I think it's safe to assume that the
Cabinet Intelligence Agency recommended us.
All right, here's the plan.
First, I'd like you to take a look at this.
This man's name is Angelica.
He's a full cyborg and a self professed commissions agent.
He's a Dutch citizen.
It has also become apparent that
he's the one we know as Angel Wing.
This terrorist is responsible for the worst
single attack in history, in terms of victims.
What proof do we have?
And what was this attack?
I'll get to that in a minute.
Angel Wing's ideology and style are consistent.
He is opposed to the fact
that a select few advanced
nations monopolise
decision-making on global issues.
Therefore, he announced that he would
set off bombs in glass-sheathed skyscrapers
somewhere in each nation where the summits would be held.
He earned his name from the fact that he
generated more victims by raining glass shards
from the explosion on the people below.
While the host nations were on high alert because of his threats,
they still could not prevent all the attacks,
since each one might occur anywhere in the country.
The investigating authorities
then tried to ascertain his
appearance from the IR system
logs in each building he attacked.
However, as a complete cyborg, he wore a different face every time,
effectively becoming a completely different individual.
This is why Angel Wing's true identity remains unknown.
If that's the case, how did you reach the conclusion that
he is a complete cyborg and not just a face-swapper?
Two months ago,
a physician in the Netherlands, who specialises
in cyborgs, accidentally put a man in a coma
during an operation to swap his cybernetic body.
Several memories were found in this person
that seemed to indicate that the man was Angel Wing.
According to the Dutch physician,
specific details about the terrorist bombings the man had committed,
and facial data of the bodies he switched to afterward,
were found among the memories extracted.
Do the IR logs from the attack site confirm this facial data?
All of the faces were present.
After wrestling for a few days with the inherent
ethical problems involved in turning over this data,
the physician reported his findings to the local police.
If only he'd reported it earlier...
That's true, but we can't blame him.
So we know this much.
With this data, why were we called to Berlin
instead of to Leeds, where the summit will be held next month?
Good question.
The authorities checked this man's past
facial data against IR systems in airports worldwide.
It was discovered that Angel Wing
always stop here in Berlin before an attack
and then, two days before the attack date,
departs from Tegel International Airport
to his destination.
For the Shanghai Summit in 2028, he departed February 17th;
for the Moscow Summit in 2029, November 25th;
and for the Paris Summit in 2030, July 13th.
These dates all follow the "two days prior" pattern.
For some reason, he has repeated the same pattern three times.
Considering that Angel Wing had shown
no other routine behaviour except his attack method,
this seems like a very unusual pattern.
What route does he use to come to Berlin?
That is unknown,
but for some reason, he always came
through Berlin before his attacks.
Therefore, it is probable that he'll
be here in Berlin again for a few days
before the upcoming summit.
During this time, we can assume that he'll be
using the same cybernetic body as the one in this data.
This is the first real chance we've had to catch him.
During the time that he's here,
we will do whatever it takes to find and collar him.
And this is how we'll accomplish that, obviously.
It makes me want to quit this mission already.
It seems I just don't get along with dogs.
That girl again.
Where does she keep going at this time of the day, alone.
not to mention in the snow?
All units, this is a routine sector check.
Confirming sectors.
Report status.
This is D1. No sign of target.
Situation normal.
This is D2. No sign of target.
Possibility of infiltration is nil.
This is D3. No sign of target.
Situation normal.
This is D4. No sign of target and situation normal.
Roger that.
Continue surveillance.
The operation will end in two days, regardless of the outcome.
If Angel Wing does not appear,
the operation will be transferred to the Leeds authorities,
and the investigation will revert to
the pursuit of a faceless terrorist.
Be vigilant; we must acquire the target in
this window of opportunity at all costs.
Roger.
D4, what's wrong?
It's just not a mission I'm suited for, that's all.
"Transparent Monster Sighted in Stations and at the Airport"?
It seems I'm not the only one bored around here.
"Asian refugees announced Dejima as an autonomous region in Japan."
I guess things are getting hairy.
What's with that girl?
Does she know who I am?
Even if she does, I have no idea why she should.
Angel, why is it that Papa hasn't shown up yet...
when his mail came two weeks ago?
"Papa"?
But I do feel his presence.
He must have another errand.
Who is it?
She's perceptive.
Could it be...
An orphanage...
So she could see me from here, huh?
Angel, I've always told Papa that there's nothing I want,
but this time I do want something.
I'm sure Papa will come back again, with a different body this time,
but to me...
Theresia, could you come downstairs for a moment?
Okay!
This must be it.
It's Papa.
I'll come see you within two weeks.
Let's meet at the usual church.
No specific date, huh.
Sorry, but I have to take a look.
Talk about bad handwriting.
"July 12th, 2030.
Papa came tonight.
Met at the church chapel."
"November 24th, 2029.
Papa came back as promised.
Christmas one month early.
The present I got at the church was a cashmere coat."
"February 11th, 2028.
Suddenly got a message from Papa.
Met at the church chapel.
Got mittens as a present."
It fits!
These dates are all the day before Angelica leaves Berlin.
This is...
"The code word for when I don't recognise
Papa because he has changed his body:
"What is the angel going to do today?"
"I'm going to rain angel feathers throughout the world."
Then this means that that girl's father... is Angel Wing!
All units, this is a routine sector check.
Confirming sectors.
Report status.
This is D1. No sign of target.
Possibility of infiltration is nil.
This is D2. No sign of target.
This is D3. No sign of target.
Situation normal.
D4, why have you changed position?
Well, there were a lot of stray dogs...
Even the 3003 model has no effect on their sense of smell.
Report if you're going to change position.
Upon confirmation, we'll issue orders.
Roger.
Are you trying to atone for having killed many innocents?
Who's there?!
Angelica!
I know you're Angel Wing!
Give it up.
What are you talking about?
I...
There's no point denying it.
We have definite proof.
Why else would the police be here?
Right?
Even after taking the lives of many because of your selfish ideals,
you still want to be a father?
There must have been mothers, and children waiting for presents
at every site where you destroyed buildings
and rained glass on your victims.
If you think you can be with your daughter
and act as if nothing has happened
after taking so many lives, you're sadly mistaken.
It's too bad, but you'll never see your daughter again.
Yeah.
You're right.
You know my daughter?
I have a request to make.
If you know her,
can you give her that package?
It's something she really wanted.
Major...
When did you turn into a saint?!
I thought about just watching you,
but you're getting sloppy!
Sorry.
How'd you know?
I couldn't put a ghost invasion key on
you like I did on Togusa, of course.
So I tapped your visual receptors.
When?
You missed it during the encoded transmission yesterday. Sloppy.
The operation is over
once we notify HQ and bring him in.
Let's go back to Japan.
Papa...
Is it you, Papa?
There was a loud noise just now.
What happened?
You... weren't able to see me.
You can't see.
Who is it?
It's you right, Papa?
I can tell.
Hey, Papa...
Papa, I'm scared.
Please answer me...
Hey, you're there right?
Papa...
What is the angel going to do today?
The angel...
The angel!
won't...
won't be going anywhere anymore.
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(the time is right)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
(the time is now)
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
all I need,
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.